A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Speeches, Post-Vice Presidential, Series M FA349
Rockefeller Archive Center
- October 6, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  Albany, New York. Dedication ceremonies for the newly renamed "Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller Empire State Plaza," formerly the South Mall. Draft, press conference transcript. Remarks by Governor Hugh Carey, program of events, clippings, story of why the Plaza cam to be built.
- October 26, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  New York City. Waldorf-Astoria Hotel. Meeting of the Rotary Area Assembly. NAR was guest speaker. Speech on John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s credo. Transcript, program, NAR's schedule for October 26.
- November 15, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  New York City. Speech on art delivered at the University Club. Transcript, memoranda, correspondence.
- January 17, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  New York City. Announcement concerning a new reproduction method for The Nelson Rockefeller Collection, Inc. Press release of remarks. Transcript of remarks. List of reporters attending.
- January 26, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  New York City. The Buckley School. NAR's remarks and introduction of Henry Kissinger to students (including his sons, Nelson, Jr., and Mark). This was NAR's last public appearance. Transcript.
- January 27, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  New York City. Waldorf-Astoria Hotel. World Antiques Market Conference. NAR was scheduled to attend the conference. Conference literature, press release of NAR's informal remarks which was issued on January 26, memoranda, correspondence concerning NAR's appearance at the conference.
- January 27, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  New York City. Press release announcing the decision to make a Manhattan retail store a permanent feature of The Nelson Rockefeller Collection, Inc. List of reporters who were sent the release on January 26.
- January 27, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  New York City. Press releases concerning the private interment service for NAR in Pocantico on January 29 and the public memorial service at Riverside Church on February 2. Statement by Hugh Morrow concerning the place of NAR's death. Memo to 5600 staff stating offices will be closed on February 2 for the memorial service. Lists of dignitaries attending memorial service. Press information sheets about the memorial service.
- January 27, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  New York City. Statement issued by Laurance Rockefeller on his brother's death.
- January 29, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  Pocantico. Interment services for NAR. Remarks by Nelson A. Rockefeller, Jr., NAR's son.
- January 29, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  Pocantico. Interment services for NAR. Remarks by Meile Rockefeller, NAR's granddaughter.
- February 2, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  New York City. Riverside Church. Memorial Service for NAR. Program for service. List of ushers.
- February 2, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  New York City. Riverside Church. Memorial Service for NAR. Remarks by Ann Rockefeller Roberts, NAR's elder daughter.
- February 2, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  New York City. Riverside Church. Memorial Service for NAR. Remarks by Rodman Rockefeller, NAR's eldest son.
- February 2, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  New York City. Riverside Church. Memorial Service for NAR. Remarks by David Rockefeller, NAR's youngest brother.
- February 2, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  New York City. Riverside Church. Memorial Service for NAR. Eulogy of NAR delivered by Henry Kissinger.
- February 9, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  New York City. Press releases and memoranda concerning NAR's will.